It's go to San Francisco. It almost kind
of late. It's stop boardings right now.
>> Okay.
>> You may leave freely, but the currency
cannot.
>> This situation appears straightforward,
almost routine, involving nothing more
than two passengers, a carry-on bag, and
a large amount of cash discovered at an
airport checkpoint. But as officers
begin asking questions and listening
carefully to the answers, it becomes
clear that this is not just about money,
but about identity, intent, and a story
that starts to unravel almost
immediately. On March 27, 2025, at
approximately 7:24 p.m., officers
responded to the West checkpoint at
Orlando International Airport after the
TSA alerted them to two passengers,
Yuzang Chen and Zin Miang, attempting to
conceal a significant amount of US
currency inside a carry-on bag. Chen and
Fang provide an explanation that sounds
detailed on the surface, but quickly
raises additional questions.
>> We're probably going to ask you some
questions.
>> How are you all?
>> Yeah, I understand there was some money
in your bag.
>> Uh, yes. I'm doing translate for him.
>> Okay. Who Who does the bag belong to?
>> Can I ask your
documentation for the money?
>> Only the only the only on the bank. We
get some money from our account and some
money is from casino.
>> Okay.
>> And this one take for the bank. [snorts]
>> It was all
>> where does it start? Right here.
>> This is I save you as your 195.
>> This money is uh
>> from the from the
in my boss give me the income. Someone
is my boss. Give me just a little bit.
>> Explain me what he said.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Because I didn't
know. So I'm used to Chinese. Ask him.
>> I myself have money. This is my money. I
have job and then uh this is my my
sister give me some money cash.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah.
>> So I'm understanding he's saying this is
his money that he earned.
>> Uh does he her his sister gave it to
him?
>> His sister gave it to him.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. And also the money is his parent
give it to sister and his sister give
him.
>> How much money did his parents give him?
>> About 7,000 7,000
>> is my money.
>> So his parent give him like almost like
7k and his sister give him almost like
8k.
>> Okay.
>> Yes.
>> 8k. Where did the rest come from?
>> Huh?
>> Where did the rest come from?
>> And the and the rest come from we go to
the gambler.
>> Casino.
>> The casino.
>> Yeah. Casino. Okay. And how much did you
win?
>> 32 3 15
>> 15. Okay.
>> And I won like 5K.
>> And you won like five. So some of yours
is in there too. Is it?
>> Yeah, it's in there too.
>> And then what did you do after the
casino and after your parents gave you
the money and everything?
>> He he should buy a he want to buy a car.
>> I need a travel. I go to Orlando.
>> So the money that you withdrew from his
account, that was the money that his
sister and his mother gave him.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Okay. And then the rest of it is from
the casino.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. And that was never deposited into
an account or anything.
>> Sorry,
>> the money from the casino was never
deposited into his account.
>> Yeah, they because they didn't they want
to give me the documents or the receipt.
They just say, "Okay, you got a card,
play a card and give me the money, but
they let us write a W9.
>> Do you have any of that paperwork from
the casino?"
>> No,
paper.
>> That's That's not possible. Yeah. Chen
and Fang are unable to produce any
receipt or proof that they actually won
the money. But this was just the
beginning of their problem. As officers
began the standard process of
inventorying the cash, they discovered
something even more incriminating.
>> They usually give you a receipt for your
earnings.
>> 102
>> about how much was it?
>> About 40,000. She has about 5,000. He
has about 40,000.
>> Okay.
>> About 15 16 of which she said was from
relatives. Another 15 from the casino.
All wrapped in rubber bands by CSA. No
documentation. He has he does have
transactions on his app for about
>> of the uh of the
>> for a few thousand. Yeah. For what he
got from the family.
>> Yeah.
>> But no documentation for the stuff from
the casino.
>> And where is your flight? Where's your
flight to?
>> It's go to San Francisco. It almost kind
of late. It stop boardings right now.
>> Okay.
>> Take it right there.
>> Sure. Yeah. Yeah.
>> I was casino was
>> uh Har in Tampa.
>> Har Tampa.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> So you you are free to leave. The money
has to stay until we can investigate
further.
>> Okay.
>> So we have to make some notifications.
>> You want to explain that to him? You you
two are free to leave, but the money has
to stay until we can do some
investigation.
>> We can.
>> So we're making a phone call.
>> Yeah.
>> To someone else. They're going to decide
if they want to come out and speak with
you further. If they don't, then you can
leave with the currency. Not a problem.
>> At this point, you're not detained. You
may leave freely, but the currency
cannot. If you would like to uh leave,
then we can go back to the office and
you can leave the currency there and so
forth. But we're making a phone call and
it shouldn't take more than a few
minutes here now to determine if they're
going to come out. If they do not want
to come out, if they do not want to come
out, then you guys leave. That's it.
Take your money. You can't go. Where you
going to go? Okay.
>> So,
>> do you have the Do you have the image?
>> Do you have the image? I'll be right
back. This is her bag. Do you have his
bag?
>> That's her bag or his. He said it was
his It was in the jacket.
>> Can I see what's in the bag?
>> Is anything How is it concealed? The
>> one reference.
>> Well, I It's just
>> Okay, that's that's all that you found.
>> Yeah,
>> that was all.
>> And how was it in the bag? Just in the
pocket.
>> She said it was wrapped in the jacket
inside the bag.
>> And now her bag has cash in it, too.
>> I didn't check. They didn't put her bag.
>> Her bag wasn't full. Yeah. When uh when
did you go to the casino?
>> Uh about yesterday.
>> Yesterday. The day before yesterday and
the day before before yesterday. We went
there like three days.
>> Yeah.
>> And you don't have any receipt or
anything? Neither of you.
>> Have you been casino before?
>> Yes, I have.
>> They give you a receipt.
>> Yes.
>> They do.
>> They just because they have the member
card.
>> Can I see your May I see your member
card?
>> You don't have to show me. But
>> yeah,
>> you lost it. Nelson Pagan,
>> you lost it.
>> Please proceed to a Facebook zero for a
message.
>> Nelson Pagan,
>> do do you have a membership card?
>> I just put in because
>> Do you have like an account for the
casino where you can pull up your
winnings?
>> The the airline is called me.
>> The airline called you? Okay.
>> I think I have I I didn't take a picture
about my member card.
>> Okay. But you check the rest of the bag.
That's all the cash that was in there.
There's nothing hidden in the liner.
>> This is
>> Yeah.
>> Gotcha. They do have reservations where
it shows that they were at the casino.
>> Michael.
>> So when you open the bag
>> when I opened the bag and then I saw
Yeah. I asked him, "How much do you have
here?" He said about 40,000.
>> It was like actually like wrapped up in
this.
>> Yeah. With the little rubber band around
there.
Sweet.
>> Haven't finished counting this. It's
going to be over 50.
>> I asked him specifically if it's over
50. No, no, no. And this texture.
>> Okay. And he's saying that
>> between 120
>> all California all different.
That's why they
>> But all three of the Oh, no. We have
William William Spencer.
Basically, we have we got money call out
and this guy's got a little over 100,000
in cash. But then with the second 50,000
in cash, uh he had three fake IDs and a
couple uh looks like fraudulent credit
cards.
>> Can you get the suitcase?
>> Yeah, they're up right now. There's free
>> and do you have some water?
>> Take a seat. I'll get you some water.
What am I? What am I?
>> Um,
he's just contained. Okay.
>> What?
>> Which means he's not
restained.
Okay.
>> Okay.
>> Where do you want them? Uh, can I touch
my phone and then call my phone?
>> You have any more IDs on you?
>> No.
>> You okay if I check your
>> Who's there?
>> Just come on over here. Okay.
>> Someone just kept my ID. You send me my
ID?
>> Yes. Yes. I'll give it to you.
>> May I see your wallet?
>> Yeah, absolutely.
>> Can you run these on telly?
>> Yes.
>> Thank you.
>> What is mine?
>> One is yours. Yeah.
>> Which one is yours?
>> This one.
>> That one's yours. Okay. Thank you.
>> Which name is the us
one?
>> Yeah.
>> Nothing in my bag. You can
>> just money.
>> Yes. Nothing ID. Nothing.
>> Money and ID.
>> What do you have?
>> What do you have those IDs?
>> Someone give me
a message.
>> Linda.
>> Wait for her to come back.
>> Yeah.
>> This is my old hat. I need to pay my
friend a lot of money. This is my always
my friend money. I need to pay my friend
a lot of money.
>> Why?
>> 120,000.
>> You have to pay your friend,000.
>> This is my always my friend money. And I
want to go to the casino owing. You
know, this is all my friend money. Oh my
god. You take everything. I I need a you
know.
>> When she comes back, we're going to
talk. Okay.
>> Yes.
>> When she comes back, let's talk.
>> You can kill me. If you take this money,
you can kill me.
>> No.
>> No, you can't. It's my old. I can pay my
friend a lot of money.
>> We'll talk about that. We'll figure out
why.
>> This is my old I have I need to pay more
money. You can show me first. I don't
know the airline. Can we take a lot of
money in here?
>> I don't know. So, I need to go to a
jail. Jo
>> right now. I want to talk to you.
>> Okay. So, later I go to Jo like a jail.
>> A jail.
>> Yeah.
>> That's why I want to talk to you. I want
to find out what's going on, but I don't
want to try to talk to you and you not
understand what I'm saying. Okay.
>> Okay. Okay. Just go.
>> No. No. Sit down. Just go. Just go. Just
go. I don't want to listen to anything.
You're taking my everything, right? Just
go.
>> You want You don't want to talk to me.
Tell me what's going on.
>> Listen, my all, you know.
>> I know. And that's why I want to know
what's going on. Okay.
>> But I can't do that till I I I really
get to talk to you. But you don't
understand everything I'm saying. Or do
you understand everything I'm saying?
>> I just need my money.
>> Do you understand everything I'm saying?
>> Yeah. I I I You can show me. You can
show me.
>> So, you're willing to talk to me?
>> You can show me. Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah, you can show me.
>> Let's give her about five more minutes.
If she doesn't show up,
>> just show me. Just show me. It's okay.
Just show me.
>> Show you.
>> Yeah. Just show me.
>> Talk to you.
>> Yeah. It's my all half.
>> There she is.
>> This is my all half.
>> Can you sit down?
>> Tell him to stay seated.
This is the one that he says is his real
one.
>> Yeah,
>> this one is also real.
>> And this came back to nothing.
>> Uh, that came back to nothing. That one
came back to another Chinese person.
>> Yeah, it's Chinese.
>> Stand up.
>> Oh my gosh.
>> Okay.
It's up to you if you're done.
>> Come with me.
>> Hold on. Let me talk to my girlfriend
something.
>> Nope.
>> Nope. We're going.
>> Yeah. Can I tell something?
>> Yeah, we got to go.
>> Look like she went to the other
>> side. Just have a seat over there. Okay.
I don't know.
>> All right. I'll I'll let you know once
everything's done. This is his his
property.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. I'll put it in.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you guys.
>> How much
or what?
>> Huh?
Hold on.
>> No. Left foot in first.
>> Can I put a disc?
>> Yeah, he's been pat down a couple times.
>> How about my cigarette?
>> What?
>> What's that? Those can't go to the jail.
>> Um,
>> I don't know um if cigarettes were
allowed to go to the jail. The
detectives put everything in your bag
now. Okay. And then whatever couldn't
go, they brought they gave it to your
your friend, your girlfriend.
>> Chen is escorted to a temporary
detainment area inside the airport. The
officers eventually discovered that Chen
does not have legal status to remain in
the United States and promptly the
immigration and customs enforcement were
notified. In the end, Yuzang Chen was
charged with fraud, impersonization,
creating or possessing fictitious
personal identification. But the
unanswered questions remain. Where did
he get the money from? And who and where
are the owners of the credit cards? But
regardless of the answers, it definitely
wasn't the best day for Chen.